<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Yet Another Boring Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://anand-iyer.github.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://anand-iyer.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2013-01-20T18:46:57-08:00</updated>
  <id>http://anand-iyer.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Anand]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Latex Tips Collection]]></title>
    <link href="http://anand-iyer.github.com/blog/2013/01/13/latex-tips-collection/"/>
    <updated>2013-01-13T18:18:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://anand-iyer.github.com/blog/2013/01/13/latex-tips-collection</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Over time, I’ve come across many useful Latex tips and tricks scattered across the internet. Here’s an attempt to collect some of those:</p>

<ul>
<li><p><a href="http://gurmeet.net/computer-science/latex-tips-n-tricks-for-conference-papers/"><strong>Tips for Conference Papers</strong></a> by Gurmeet Singh <br/>
A nice set of tricks that saves your life at the last minute during deadlines.</p></li>
<li><p><a href="http://www.read.seas.harvard.edu/~kohler/latex.html"><strong>Latex Usage Notes</strong></a> by Eddie Kohler <br/>
Solutions for common Latex problems, tips on proper formatting, etc.</p></li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Syncing folders outside Dropbox folder]]></title>
    <link href="http://anand-iyer.github.com/blog/2012/10/16/syncing-folders-outside-dropbox-folder/"/>
    <updated>2012-10-16T18:27:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anand-iyer.github.com/blog/2012/10/16/syncing-folders-outside-dropbox-folder</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>A big complaint I have about Dropbox is that unlike SugarSync, it does allow me to sync any folder in my computer (essentially, I need to place the folders I want to be synced inside the “Dropbox” folder).</p>

<p>Recently, I found a workaround for this problem. Here’s the trick to syncing any folder in your computer: softlink the folder to your Dropbox folder!</p>

<p>If you’re using a Mac (or Linux), just use the following command:</p>

<pre><code>ln -s /full-path-to-folder/file-to-sync ~/Dropbox/desired-folder-name
</code></pre>

<p>That’s it, from now on, all file(s) in the actual path would now sync with Dropbox.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doxygen and OSX: Graphviz and other errors]]></title>
    <link href="http://anand-iyer.github.com/blog/2011/10/09/doxygen-and-osx-graphviz-and-other-errors/"/>
    <updated>2011-10-09T18:32:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://anand-iyer.github.com/blog/2011/10/09/doxygen-and-osx-graphviz-and-other-errors</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I’m a big fan of <a href="http://www.doxygen.org/">Doxygen</a>. I use it all the time to generate and analyze call trees. Recently, I wanted to use it in my MacbookPro for analyzing an open source project. There is a binary for SnowLeopard <a href="http://www.stack.nl/~dimitri/doxygen/download.html">here</a> that works in Lion too, but it was throwing lots of errors regarding Graphviz. Here are two things that I had to do to make it finally work:</p>

<ul>
<li><p>For some reason, long file names do not work in OSX. By default, Doxygen uses long names. So you need to set the <code>SHORT_NAMES</code> to <code>YES</code> in your doxygen file. If you are using the Wizard (GUI), then save your settings file (<code>File-&gt;Save</code>), and then manually edit the file in a text editor.</p></li>
<li><p>GraphViz is included in the dmg file. You need to set appropriate path to the dot file for graphviz to work. Try setting it to <code>‘/Applications/Doxygen.app/Contents/Resources’</code>. If that fails, then use macports to install graphviz, and use that path.</p></li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
